A Guide to the John S. and James L. Knight Foundation records, RG 5 Program Files, Subgroup: Grant Files (A-K) FA1783
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Technology and Media Innovation, 2012-2018; 4; 14.81 Cubic Feet 39 letter document boxes
  - Democracy Works - Digital Tools for Election Information (2016-53580), 2016-2017 (Box 40, Folder 556)
  - Democracy Works - Scaling Democracy Works (2014-49628), 2012-2016 (Box 40, Folder 557)
  - The Des Moines Register - Iowa Electorate: Engaged and Energized (2015-51208) (Box 41, Folder 559)
  - District of Columbia Board of Elections - Erase the Line (2015-51042) (Box 44, Folder 596)
  - DocumentCloud - DocumentCloud Platform (2017-55172) (Box 44, Folder 603)
  - e.thePeople - Informed Voting from Start to Finish (2015-51023), 2013-2016 (Box 45, Folder 620)
  - Evenly Distributed LLC - Libraries and Open Hardware (2015-50329), 2012-2015 (Box 47, Folder 650)
  - Experimental Station - Citizen's Police Data Project (2015-51947), 2013-2016 (Box 47, Folder 655)
  - Fair Elections Legal Network - Vote Worker Data Project (2015-51237) (Box 48, Folder 659)
  - Fergus Pitt - Journalism in Virtual Reality (2014-49880), 2012-2014 (Box 48, Folder 668)
  - Foundation Center - Visualizing Philanthropic Funding for Libraries (2016-52994), 2015-2017 (Box 50, Folder 701)
  - University of Texas at Austin - International Symposium on Online Journalism (ISOJ) (2015-51210) (Box 53, Folder 735)
  - Free Library of Philadelphia - Cultureshare (2016-52838) (Box 53, Folder 738)
  - Friends of the Dallas Public Library Inc. - Storytellers Without Borders: Activating the Next Generation of Community Journalists Through Library Engagement (2016-53151), 2014-2017 (Box 54, Folder 746)
  - Georgia State University - ATLmaps: Deep Mapping the Stories of Your City (2016-52834), 2015-2016 (Box 57, Folder 781)
  - GoodCity - Documents Empower Project (2016-52099), 2014-2016 (Box 58, Folder 798)
  - GovLoop - GovLoop Academy (2015-51209), 2013-2015 (Box 58, Folder 802)
  - The Greater Washington Educational Telecommunications Association - NewsTracker.org (2017-54456) (Box 59, Folder 830)
  - Higher Media, Inc. - Open Contracts (2015-51972), 2013-2015 (Box 61, Folder 853)
    Visible Contracts, an interactive tool to explore the city of Philadelphia's procurement data.
  - Hollaback - HeartMob Online Platform (2015-50929), 2012-2017 (Box 62, Folder 867)
    A platform to provide those esperiencing online harassment with a safe way to report incidents and receive support from volunteers.
  - How Wrong You Are - How Wrong You Are (2014-49655), 2012-2015 (Box 62, Folder 874)
    Promote data journalism and audience engagement by testing new tools for online quiz platforms.
  - Institute of Contemporary Art Miami, Inc. - Digital Content Strategy and Production (2017-53953) (Box 64, Folder 902)
  - Internet Archive - Political Advertisement Tracker Archive (2015-51005), 2015-2016 (Box 66, Folder 920)
  - Internet Archive - Building Libraries Together (2015-50350), 2012-2015 (Box 66, Folder 921)
  - Investigative Reporters and Editors Inc. - California's Campaign Finance Database (2015-51285), 2012-2016 (Box 66, Folder 927)
  - Jorge M. Perez Art Museum of Miami Dade County, Inc. - Augmented Reality: Bringing Art to Life (2017-54029) (Box 67, Folder 948)
  - Joostware AI Research Corporation - Who Said What (2017-54416) (Box 68, Folder 957)
    Tool to identify who is speaking in video and audio news to be used by fact checkers.
  - Kavya Sukumar - Chitram (2015-51971), 2013-2015 (Box 68, Folder 964)
    Data visualization in journalism. Chitram is a tool that creates animated data vizualization videos.
  - KQED Inc. - Improving Youth Civic Engagement through KQED Learn (2017-54389) (Box 69, Folder 974)
- Learning and Impact, 2009-2018; 5; 2.28 Cubic Feet 6 letter document boxes
  The Learning and Impact program focuses on assessment and research within the Foundation. Its goal is to review investments to determine how they are impacting and promoting the goals of the organization.
  - The American University - Marginalized Communities on Twitter as News and as Journalists (2016-53341), 2017 (Box 7, Folder 97)
  - Board of Trustees of the Leland Stanford Junior University - The Fragmentation of News Interactions on Digital Devices (2017-54227) (Box 15, Folder 204)
  - Board of Trustees of the Leland Stanford Junior University - Stanford Project on Social Media and Democracy (2017-54749), 2014-2017 (Box 15, Folder 206)
  - Data Foundation - Corporate Data Philanthropy (2017-54877) (Box 40, Folder 546)
  - Early Childhood Initiative Foundation - Strategic Plan (2011-0114), 2009-2012 (Box 45, Folder 624)
  - Grantmakers Concerned with Immigrants and Refugees - General Support (2013-47410) (Box 59, Folder 809)
  - Grantmakers for Effective Organizations - Membership (2016-53640), 2016-2017 (Box 59, Folder 810)
  - Grantmakers for Effective Organizations - General Support (2015-51708) (Box 59, Folder 811)
  - Grantmakers for Effective Organizations - Membership (2017-55405), 2017-2018 (Box 59, Folder 812)
  - Grantmakers for Effective Organizations - General Support (2013-47409) (Box 59, Folder 813)
  - GuideStar - GuideStar 2020 (2016-53288) (Box 60, Folder 836)
  - GuideStar - GuideStar 2020 (2015-51305), 2013-2017 (Box 60, Folder 838)
- Other, 2003-2018; 6; 16.33 Cubic Feet 43 letter document boxes
  This series includes grants that fall outside of the Knight Foundation's primary program areas. Grants are arranged into groupings that represent the Trustee-Advised Grant Program, the Emergency/Impact Fund, Communications, and Membership.
  - Trustee-Advised Grant Program, 2003-2018; 1
    - A Better Chance, Inc. - General Operating Support (Borges) (2013-47829), 2013-2014 (Box 2, Folder 17)
    - ACCESS, Inc. - Community Outreach (Considine) (2017-53975) (Box 2, Folder 23)
    - ACCESS, Inc. - Crisis Shelter (Considine) (2017-54240) (Box 2, Folder 24)
    - Akron Art Museum - Art Program Support (Considine) (2017-53976) (Box 3, Folder 32)
    - Akron Children's Hospital Foundation - Neonatal Intensive Care Fund (Considine) (2017-53971) (Box 3, Folder 37)
    - Akron Children's Hosptial Foundation - General Operating Support (Considine) (2016-52837) (Box 3, Folder 38)
    - Akron Children's Hosptial Foundation - Initiatives and Research to Support Infant Mortality, Low Birth Weight Babies, and Substance Dependent Newborns (Considine) (2014-50370), 2015 (Box 3, Folder 39)
    - Akron Community Foundation - Trustee Advised Departure Grant (Briggs) (2014-48509) (Box 3, Folder 41)
      Donor Advised Fund in honor of Robert Briggs' service to the Knight Foundation to support grassroots nonprofit organizations in Akron.
    - Akron Community Service Center and Urban League - Neighborhood Outreach Initiatives and Minority Entrepreneurship Forums (Considine) (2015-50367) (Box 3, Folder 42)
    - Akron Creative, Inc. - The Nightline Cinema (Mayer) (2017-54420) (Box 3, Folder 44)
    - Akron Metropolitan Housing Authority Community Action Network - Reach Opportunity Center at Summit Lake (Crutchfield) (2015-51033) (Box 4, Folder 48)
    - ALS Association, Greater New York Chapter - In Honor and Memory of Claire Tow (2014-49339) (Box 4, Folder 59)
    - Alzheimer's Disease and Related Disorders Association, Inc. - Dancing Stars of Central Georgia Benefit (Olson) (2017-54562) (Box 4, Folder 60)
    - Alzheimer's Disease and Related Disorders Association, Inc. - Dancing Stars of Central Georgia Benefit (Olson) (2014-48257) (Box 4, Folder 61)
    - American Civil Liberties Union Foundation - Memorial Gift in Honor of Patricia Derian (Carter) (2016-52791) (Box 5, Folder 67)
    - American Society for the Prevention of Cruelty to Animals (ASPCA) - General Operating Support (Steiger) (2014-50151), 2014-2015 (Box 6, Folder 92)
    - Archbishop Hoban High School Inc. - Wellness Initiative (Considine) (2017-53972) (Box 7, Folder 106)
    - Archbishop Hoban High School Inc. - Wellness Initiative (Considine) (2014-48021) (Box 7, Folder 111)
    - ArtsNow - General Operating Support (Mayer) (2017-54616) (Box 9, Folder 121)
    - The Asheville School - Cody Fund (Crane) (2014-49195), 2012-2014 (Box 9, Folder 128)
    - Bainbridge Recovery Club - General Operating Support (Mayer) (2017-55312) (Box 11, Folder 154)
    - Baldwin Wallace University - Graduate School of Business (Briggs) (2014-48502), 2011-2014 (Box 11, Folder 155)
    - Baptist Health South Florida Foundation, Inc. - Neonatal Intensive Care Unit Technology Needs (Rodriguez) (2014-49944) (Box 11, Folder 157)
    - Bascom Palmer Eye Institute - General Operating Support (Powell) (2014-48495) (Box 11, Folder 160)
    - Battered Women's Shelter - Health Clinic (Considine) (2017-53978) (Box 11, Folder 161)
    - Boston Area Reggio Inspired Network - General Operating Support (Palfrey) (2017-54874) (Box 16, Folder 214)
    - Boston Public Library Foundation - Support Library Outreach and President's Initiatives (Palfrey) (2012-0207) (Box 16, Folder 216)
    - Boston Ballet - General Operating Support (Ito) (2017-55339) (Box 16, Folder 218)
    - Boys and Girls Clubs of Central Georgia - General Operating Support (Olson) (2013-42984) (Box 16, Folder 221)
    - Boys and Girls Clubs of the Western Reserve, Inc. - Scholarships to 2014 Bud Rogers Youth-of-the-Year Finalists (Crutchfield) (2014-48312), 2011-2015 (Box 16, Folder 222)
    - Boy Scouts of America (Mecklenburg County Council) - General Operating Support (Crane) (2014-49192), 2012-2014 (Box 16, Folder 223)
    - Breakthrough Miami, Inc. - General Operating Support (Stamps) (2012-0312) (Box 16, Folder 229)
    - Carnegie Institute - Teenie Harris Collection (Crutchfield) (2014-48671) (Box 18, Folder 252)
    - Charlotte Symphony Orchestra Society - General Operating Support (Crane) (2014-49196), 2011-2014 (Box 22, Folder 299)
    - Chez Bushwick, Inc. - Dance Education and Training (Ibarguen) (2013-47908), 2012-2014 (Box 22, Folder 301)
    - Chez Bushwick, Inc. - Dance Education and Training (Ibarguen) (2012-3682), 2012-2014 (Box 22, Folder 303)
    - Chicago Tech Academy - Inner City Technology and Entrepreneurship (Ito) (2016-53412) (Box 23, Folder 311)
    - Christmas in April, Summit County - General Operating Support (Crutchfield) (2006-0161) (Box 23, Folder 316)
    - Christopher Columbus High School - Performing Arts and Media Center (Rodriguez) (2014-49943) (Box 23, Folder 317)
    - Christopher Columbus High School - Performing Arts and Media Center (Rodriguez) (2017-55318) (Box 23, Folder 318)
    - CUNY Graduate School of Journalism Foundation Inc. - General Operating Support (Steiger) (2017-54775) (Box 26, Folder 368)
    - CUNY Graduate School of Journalism Foundation Inc. - General Operating Support (Steiger) (2015-51901) (Box 26, Folder 372)
    - Collective Shift - Connected Learning Programs (Palfrey) (2016-53346) (Box 28, Folder 399)
    - Collective Shift - Connected Learning Programs (Palfrey) (2017-55280) (Box 28, Folder 402)
    - Committee to Protect Journalists Inc. - General Operating Support (Steiger) (2017-54985) (Box 28, Folder 403)
    - Communities In Schools of Charlotte Mecklenburg - Myers Park High School (Nelson) (2014-49922) (Box 29, Folder 410)
    - Communities In Schools of Charlotte Mecklenburg - Myers Park High School (Nelson) (2017-55301) (Box 29, Folder 415)
    - Community Foundation for Palm Beach and Martin Counties - Informed and Engaged Communities (2009-0269), 2009-2013 (Box 29, Folder 417-418)
    - Community Foundation for Southeast Michigan - Departure Grant (Noland) (2014-48464), 2012-2014 (Box 30, Folder 427)
    - Community Foundation for Southeast Michigan - Eugene Driker Yiddish Literature Fund (Ibarguen) (2014-48928), 2014-2015 (Box 30, Folder 428)
    - Community Foundation of Central Georgia Inc. - Macon Telegraph Education Together Scholarship Fund (Olson) (2017-53987) (Box 32, Folder 440)
    - Community Foundation of Central Georgia Inc. - Beverly Blake Fund (Ibarguen) (2016-52805) (Box 32, Folder 441)
    - Community School of the Arts - Arts Education in the Charlotte-Mecklenburg Region (Nelson) (2017-55298) (Box 35, Folder 474)
    - Community Television Foundation of South Florida, Television Station WPBT - Viewpoint Program with Henry Mack (Ibarguen) (2014-50136), 2012-2015 (Box 35, Folder 475)
    - Committee to Protect Journalists Inc. - General Operating Support (Steiger) (2017-54985) (Box 35, Folder 477)
    - Corktown Community Development Fund - General Operating Support for Ponyride (Ibarguen) (2014-48104) (Box 36, Folder 489)
    - Council on Foreign Relations, Chez Bushwick, Inc. - Annual Campaign Fund (Ibarguen) (2013-47908), 2013-2014 (Box 37, Folder 500)
    - Council on Foreign Relations - Annual Campaign Fund (Ibarguen) (2012-3683) (Box 37, Folder 501)
    - Cranbrook Education Community - General Operating Support (Noland) (2014-48375), 2011-2014 (Box 38, Folder 515)
    - Creative Commons Corporation - General Operating Support (Ito) (2017-55360) (Box 38, Folder 517)
    - Crisis Assistance Ministry - General Operating Support (Crane) (2014-49197), 2012-2014 (Box 38, Folder 522)
    - Detroit Riverfront Conservancy - General Operating Support (Noland) (2004-0254) (Box 42, Folder 578)
    - Detroit Symphony Orchestra Hall, Inc. - General Operating Support (Noland) (2014-48378), 2011-2014 (Box 42, Folder 581)
    - Diocese of Southeast Florida Inc., St. Philips Episcopal Church - Arts and Culture Program (Rodriguez) (2017-55317) (Box 44, Folder 595)
    - Electronic Frontier Foundation, Inc. - General Operating Support (Ito) (2017-55359) (Box 46, Folder 633)
    - Electronic Privacy Information Center - General Operating Support (Ito) (2017-55358) (Box 46, Folder 634)
    - Electronic Privacy Information Center - General Operating Support (Ito) (2014-48633) (Box 46, Folder 635)
    - Emma Willard School - Annual Fund (Crane) (2014-49193), 2012-2014 (Box 46, Folder 640)
    - Essex Art Center - Informed and Engaged Communities (Palfrey) (2014-49436) (Box 47, Folder 649)
    - FJC, A Foundation of Philanthropic Funds - Memorial Gift to the Stephen J. Rose Legacy Fund (Bell-Rose) (2014-48490), 2011-2014 (Box 49, Folder 674)
    - FJC, A Foundation of Philanthropic Funds - Memorial Gift to the Stephen J. Rose Legacy Fund (Bell-Rose) (2014-49638) (Box 49, Folder 675)
    - Florida Cultural Alliance - Michael Spring (2013-47750), 2011-2013 (Box 49, Folder 676)
    - Foundation for MetroWest - Youth in Philanthropy Program (Austen) (2014-49700) (Box 51, Folder 707)
    - Foundation for the Carolinas - Donor Advised Fund (Patterson) (2015-51842), 2015-2016 (Box 51, Folder 715)
    - Foundation for the Carolinas - Project L.I.F.T. (Nelson) (2014-49923), 2014-2015 (Box 51, Folder 717)
    - Foundation for the Carolinas - Project L.I.F.T. (Nelson) (2017-55300) (Box 52, Folder 721)
    - Foundation for the Carolinas - Donor Advised Fund (Nelson) (2009-0256), 2009-2017 (Box 52, Folder 722-723)
    - Four Rivers Center for the Performing Arts - Construction (Black) (2003-0343) (Box 53, Folder 729)
    - Featured Atlas Productions, Inc. - Rashaun Mitchell, Silas Reiner, and Dancework (Ibarguen) (2013-47907) (Box 53, Folder 730)
    - Featured Atlas Productions, Inc. - Rashaun Mitchell, Silas Reiner, and Dancework (Ibarguen) (2012-3684) (Box 53, Folder 731)
    - Fresh Air Fund - General Operating Support (Steiger) (2014-50150) (Box 53, Folder 740)
    - Georgia Behavioral Health Services, Inc. - General Operating Support for the River Edge Foundation (Olson) (2017-54591) (Box 57, Folder 779)
    - Girl Scouts of Historic Georgia, Inc. - 2015 Women of Distinction Awards (Ibarguen) (2015-50397) (Box 57, Folder 786)
    - Give Direct Inc. - Support Impoverished Families in Kenya (Hughes) (2014-49971), 2012-2014 (Box 57, Folder 789)
    - Heart Tutoring - General Operating Support (Nelson) (2017-55302) (Box 60, Folder 848)
    - Hopewell Fund - Economic Security Project (Hughes) (2017-53922) (Box 62, Folder 869)
    - Hopewell Fund - Basic Income Collaborative (Hughes) (2016-53318) (Box 62, Folder 870)
    - Jorge Mas Canosa Freedom Foundation Inc. - Inaugural Fall Challenge Golf Tournament (2017-54683) (Box 68, Folder 956)
  - Emergency/Impact Fund, 2010-2017; 2
    - American Red Cross, Greater Miami and the Keys Chapter - Texas Flooding Disaster Relief (2017-54889) (Box 6, Folder 84)
    - American Red Cross, Central Midwest Georgia Chapter - Texas Flooding Disaster Relief (2017-54890) (Box 6, Folder 85)
    - American Red Cross, Greater Miami and the Keys Chapter - Louisiana Flooding Disaster Relief (2016-53130) (Box 6, Folder 86)
    - American Red Cross, Central Midwest Georgia Chapter - Louisiana Flooding Disaster Relief (2016-53132) (Box 6, Folder 87)
    - Central Florida Foundation, Inc. - Better Together Fund, Orlando Club Shooting (2016-52882) (Box 20, Folder 280)
    - Community Foundation for Southeast Michigan, Wayne State University - The Honorable Gerald E. Rosen Scholarship for Community Commitment Fund (2015-51226), 2010-2015 (Box 30, Folder 424)
    - Council on Foundations - Scenario Planning Exercise (2017-54730) (Box 37, Folder 502)
    - DataKind - Scale DataKind's Programs (2014-49166), 2013-2017 (Box 40, Folder 548)
    - Digital Public Library of America - Uncovered States (2015-50607), 2013-2017 (Box 43, Folder 590)
    - Digital Library of America - Born Digital Newspaper Publications (2015-51075), 2013-2015 (Box 43, Folder 591)
    - Florida International University Foundation Inc. - Hurricane Maria Relief Efforts (2017-55093) (Box 49, Folder 679)
    - Foundation for New England Initiatives - Hurricane Maria Relief (2017-55120) (Box 51, Folder 708)
    - Friends of the Miami-Dade Public Library, Inc. - Congressman John Lewis: MARCH Book Reimbursement (2017-54642) (Box 54, Folder 748)
    - Friends of the Miami-Dade Public Library, Inc. - Congressman John Lewis: A Conversation on Civil Rights (2016-53667) (Box 54, Folder 749)
    - Fundacion Educativa Carlos M. Castaneda, Inc. - Lecture Cycle (2017-53903) (Box 55, Folder 763)
    - Georgetown University - The Free Speech Project (2017-54338) (Box 56, Folder 777)
    - Georgetown University - Survey on Trust in American Institutions (2017-55274) (Box 56, Folder 778)
    - The Greater Washington Educational Telecommunications Association - The Vietnam War: Ken Burns Documentary (2016-52535), 2013-2016 (Box 59, Folder 831)
    - Hartford Foundation for Public Giving - Latino Endowment Fund (2017-54388) (Box 60, Folder 845)
    - Harvest Hope Food Bank - Hurricane Joaquin (2015-51694) (Box 60, Folder 846)
    - History Making Productions, CultureSource - Comeback: Bankruptcy and the Rebirth of America's City (2017-54522) (Box 62, Folder 865)
    - Independent Sector - 2015 Conference Support (2015-50717), 2013-2015 (Box 63, Folder 888)
    - Independent Sector - Website and Digital Strategy (2014-49667), 2013-2016 (Box 63, Folder 890)
    - Juntos y Unidos por Puerto Rico Inc. - Hurricane Maria Relief Effort (2017-55145) (Box 68, Folder 959)
  - Communications, 2011-2017; 3
    - Communication Network - 2017 Conference Support (2017-54197) (Box 29, Folder 412)
    - Communication Network - 2016 Conference Support (2016-52385) (Box 29, Folder 413)
    - Communication Network - 2015 Conference Support (2015-50705) (Box 29, Folder 414)
    - Council on Foundations - 2015 Annual Conference Sponsorship (2015-50903) (Box 37, Folder 506)
    - Council on Foundations - Conference Mobile Applications (2013-43083), 2011-2013 (Box 37, Folder 508)
    - Foundation Center - Idea Connection Systems Innovation Workshops (2017-54131) (Box 50, Folder 699)
  - Membership, 2005-2017; 4
    - Council of Michigan Foundation Inc. - 2016 Associate Membership (2017-54196) (Box 37, Folder 497)
    - Council on Foundations - 2016 Membership (2016-52268) (Box 37, Folder 503)
    - Council on Foundations - 2016 Annual Conference (2016-52349) (Box 37, Folder 504)
    - Council on Foundations - 2017 Membership (2016-53564) (Box 37, Folder 505)
    - Council on Foundations - Annual Membership Dues (2013-47787) (Box 37, Folder 509)
    - Council of Michigan Foundations Inc. - 2016 Associate Membership (2016-52078) (Box 37, Folder 511)
    - Council of Michigan Foundations Inc. - Annual Membership (2013-47538) (Box 37, Folder 512)
    - Delaware Valley Grantmakers - 2013 Membership (2013-43949) (Box 40, Folder 553)
    - Delaware Valley Grantmakers - 2012 Membership (2012-0236) (Box 40, Folder 555)
    - DonorsChoose.org - Gift Cards for the Florida Philanthropic Network Summit (2016-53713), 2016-2017 (Box 44, Folder 599)
    - DonorsChoose.org - Gift Cards for the Florida Philanthropic Network Summit (2016-52162) (Box 44, Folder 605)
    - Florida Philanthropic Network - 2016 Membership (2016-52104) (Box 50, Folder 690)
    - Florida Philanthropic Network - 2018 Summit Support (2017-54223) (Box 50, Folder 691)
    - Florida Philanthropic Network - President and CEO Transition (2016-52878) (Box 50, Folder 692)
    - Florida Philanthropic Network - Community Foundation Programming and Support (2016-53004) (Box 50, Folder 693)
    - Florida Philanthropic Network - 2017 Membership (2016-53565), 2016-2017 (Box 50, Folder 694)
    - Foundation Center - 2016 Membership (2016-52073) (Box 50, Folder 700)
    - Foundation Center - 2017 Membership (2016-53604), 2016-2017 (Box 50, Folder 702)
    - Foundation Center - Free Resources (2014-48004) (Box 50, Folder 703)
    - Grant Managers Network - 2016 Membership (2016-52118) (Box 59, Folder 816)
    - Grant Managers Network - 2017 Membership (2016-53585) (Box 59, Folder 817)
    - Grant Managers Network - 2014 Membership (2014-48827) (Box 59, Folder 818)
    - Grassroots Grantmakers - Membership (2012-0413), 2012-2013 (Box 59, Folder 819)
    - Greater Miami Progress Foundation - Greater Miami Chamber of Commerce Dues (2005-0017) (Box 59, Folder 824)
    - GuideStar - 2017 Charity Check Subscription (2016-53586), 2016-2017 (Box 60, Folder 837)
    - Hispanics in Philanthropy - 2017 Membership (2017-54070) (Box 61, Folder 855)
    - Hispanics in Philanthropy - 2016 Membership (2016-52134) (Box 61, Folder 856)
    - Hispanics in Philanthropy - 2013 Membership (2013-47166) (Box 61, Folder 858)
    - HistoryMiami Museum - 2017 Committee of 100 Membership (2017-53804) (Box 62, Folder 866)
    - Independent Sector - 2017 Membership (2016-53563), 2013-2016 (Box 63, Folder 887)
    - Independent Sector - 2016 Membership (2015-51823) (Box 63, Folder 889)
    - Independent Sector - 2014 Membership (2013-47637), 2012-2013 (Box 63, Folder 891)